

## **INFORMATION**

E-mail: krzys.orczykagmail.com Phone: +48 600 559 152 Polish Phone: +45 55 20 88 76 Danish

### Courses

- CNC machine tools course 23.05.2021
- SPACE BGA ESC/REF 2020 soldering course
- Certified IPC Specialist 7711/7721 25.02.2020
- Routers and switches service course Cisco 12.05.2021
- SEP to G-1E with exam 24.09.2021
- Wizzair (Navitaire) Departure system

## **FOREIGN LANGUAGES**

English - Fluent Polish - First Language

# **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

Volunteer in a student bar at SDU as a bartender

# Hobby

- Glider Pilot
- Scuba Diving on PADI license OWD
- Inshore Skipper on ISSA license
- Electronics
- Programming
- 3D modeling

# Krzysztof Orczyk

# **Career Summary**

I'm a second-year electronic engineering student at SDU with experience in the assembly of electrical and electronic installations, IT support and Programing.

Having numerous professional qualifications related to the operation of electrical devices, network administration and configuration of computer equipment.

Highly developed interpersonal skills, efficient adaptation to the new environment, proactive attitude focused on searching for innovative solutions.

# Work experiences

#### LS AIRPORT SERVICES • assisting ticketed passengers during

Pax Agent

June 2022 - September 2022

- check-in, helping them check luggage and print boarding passes, and ensuring that they have proper documentation to board the plane or
- · Boarding passengers at gate

#### **ODERON**

IT SUPPORT

Accumulation of experience, and undergoing apprenticeship. May 2021 - 2023

- Assembly, installation and technical support for servers
- Service desk
- Installation of surveillance cameras Building an internet network of an ophthalmic hospital
- Programming in C#, C, Java, Python
- SQL server

## Soft skills

- Communication
- Problem-solving
- Research
- Collaboration / Teamwork Embedded systems
- Attention to detail
- Adaptability

## Hard skills

- Data structures and algorithms
- Testing and debugging
- DevOps

## Education

#### **HIGH SCHOOL**

Electronics technician specialization

September 2018 -April 2022

#### **UNIVERSITY**

Bachelor engineering in electronics

- 2 year

September 2022 - now

# **Professional** competence

- Technical ability
- Interpersonal skills
- Adaptability
- Logical and critical thinking
- Flexibility and creativity
- hard-working
- Resistance to stress
- Ability to work in a team
- Good manners
- Diligence and willingness to develop
- well-organised